

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

# PERSONAL DETAILS

D.O.B

22 st April 1981

Contact:

Tel: +48 (733) 013 108

<u>Email:</u> rafalxpl@gmail.com

Place of birth: Białystok, Polanc

Nationality:

### PORTFOLIO

visual3design.com

visual3design.com/WTM

### INTERESTS:

Gaming, Illustration, Photography, Automotive

### PROFILE

**Bē** Behance: behance.net/rafalxpl

Deviantart rafalxpl.deviantart.com

in LinkedIn rafal-karluk-a141b149

### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

 $I^\prime m$  a Design Director with 17 years of graphic design and leadership experience in the branding, marketing, advertising and webdesign.

My professional interests include involvement in the design community and design collaboration. I have more than 5 years experience working as a responsive web designer.

I am currently available for freelance or full time work.

### EDUCATION

2006-2007 Chicago, USA	0	EAST-WEST UNIVERSITY CHICAGO ESL course
<b>2003-2006</b> Łódź, Poland	0	STUDY OF COMPUTER GRAPHICS IN LODZ 3D Animation - Web Design
2001-2003 Białystok Poland	0	SCHOOL OF INFORMATICS Windows Server Administrator, Web Design
1996-2001 Suprasl, Poland	Ó	HIGH SCHOOL OF ART ACADEMY Visual arts, especially illustration, painting, photography, sculpture, and graphic design

#### EXPERIENCE

2013-2017 Schaumburg	0	WEBTOMED, L.L.C. Web Designer - Responsive Medical Website Designer, Identity, UX UI Design
2012 - 2013 Chicago	0	KREATE Freelancer / Web Designer , Identity, UX UI Design
2011 - 2012 Chicago	0	DMC, INC. Freelancer / Web Designer , Identity, UX UI Design
2008 - 2011 Chicago	0	VISUAL3DESIGN Graphic Designer / Web Designer , Identity, UX UI Design
2007 - 2008 Chicago	0	MAGAZYN "PLUS" Graphic Designer
2006 - 2007 Chicago	Ö	BLUEBOX Graphic Designer

## SKILLSET

Design Software (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign)
Print Design - color space, printing processes, color separation, grid layout
Color Theory
Typography
Responsive Web Design
Web Design/Basic HTML & CSS